<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoslingLovelaceApplicationBasic</string>
    <string name="Lovelace">Augusta Ada King, Countess of Lovelace, December 10, 1815 - November 27, 1852, formerly known as Augusta Ada Byron (Augusta) Ada Byron), commonly known as Ada Lovelace, is the daughter of the famous English poet Byron, a mathematician. The founder of the computer program, established the concept of loops and subroutines.
        To formulate an algorithm for the calculation program, the first program design flow chart written was cherished as "the first person to write a program to a computer." To commemorate the significant impact of Ada Augusta on modern computer and software engineering, the US Department of Defense named the high-level, high-level programming language that has been developed over the past 20 years as the Ada language, which is recognized as the fourth. The main representative of the computer language.
        In 1842, Ada Lovelace, known as the Digital Queen, wrote the first computer program in history.
        In 1834, Adas friend, British mathematician, inventor and mechanical engineer Charles Babbage, invented an analysis machine; Ada was working on the algorithm for the analysis machine, and in 1843 The worlds first algorithm was announced in the year.
        The Babezi analyzer was later considered to be the earliest computer prototype, and Adas algorithm was considered the earliest computer program and software.
        In 1852, Ada died of excessive blood loss in order to treat cervical cancer, and was 36 years old. Coincidentally, she and her father, Byron, died at the same age, and died of excessive blood loss during treatment. She left two sons and one daughter, Anne Brant, a noble woman.
        According to her last words, Ada was buried in the church of St. Maria Magdalene in Nottinghams Hucknow, sleeping next to her father.</string>
    <string name="Gosling">James Gosling is a software expert born in Canada on May 19, 1955. He is one of the co-founders of the Java programming language and is generally recognized as the father of Java.
When he was 12, he was able to design an electronic game console to help neighbors repair the harvester. In the university, he worked as a program development student in the Department of Astronomy. In 1977, he obtained a bachelors degree in computer science from the University of Calgary, Canada. In 1983, he received a doctorate in computer science from Carnegie Mellon University.
The title of the doctoral thesis is: The Algebraic Manipulation of Constraints. After graduating, he worked at IBM and designed IBM first-generation workstation NeWS system, but it was not taken seriously. Later transferred to Sun. In 1990, he collaborated with Patrick Naughton and Mike Sheridan on the Green Plan and later developed a language called Oak, which was later renamed Java. At the end of 1994, James Gosling presented Java programs at the Technology, Education and Design Conference in Silicon Valley. In 2000, Java became the most popular computer language in the world.
In April 2009, Sun was acquired by Oracle. Gosling announced his departure from Oracle in April 2010.
On March 29, 2011, Gosling announced on his personal blog that he would join Google.
On August 30, 2011, just a few months after joining Google, Gosling announced his departure from Google on his personal blog, joining Liquid Robotics, a startup company engaged in marine robotics research, as chief software architect.
Founded in May 2011 as Scalas Typesafe Inc., Gosling was hired as a company consultant.</string>
</resources>
